(Sheldon:)Only a suggestion. A catch in your throat
would work just as well.
[GROANS]
[VOICE CRACKING] "But it is a fact
that it's a privilege to know you.
Totally."
(Sheldon:)Maybe you should put on
your Juicy pants again.
(Judge:)Pay the cashier.
(Penny:)Sheldon Cooper.
Good morning, Your Honor.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Sheldon Cooper appearing in pro se.
That is to say, representing himself.
(Judge:)I know what it means.
I went to law school.
(Sheldon:)And yet you wound up in traffic court.
(Sheldon:)If it would please the court,
I'd like to begin with an opening statement.
(Judge:)The court would advise you
to make it quick.
(Judge:)The court had a dicey-looking
breakfast burrito and just took an Imodium.
(Sheldon:)Very well. A quick opening statement.
(Sheldon:)Like a milking stool,
my case rests on three legs.